const ASIA = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'Afghanistan',
      answer: 'Kabul',
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: 'Armenia',
      answer: 'Yerevan',
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: 'Azerbaijan',
      answer: 'Baku',
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: 'Bahrain',
      answer: 'Manama',
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: 'Bangladesh',
      answer: 'Dhaka',
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: 'Bhutan',
      answer: 'Thimphu',
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: 'Brunei',
      answer: 'Bandar Seri Begawan',
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: 'Cambodia',
      answer: '	Phnom Penh',
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: 'China',
      answer: 'Beijing',
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: 'Cyprus',
      answer: 'Nicosia',
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: 'Georgia',
      answer: 'Tbilisi',
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: 'India',
      answer: 'New Delhi',
    },
    {
      id: 13,
      question: 'Indonesia',
      answer: 'Jakarta',
    },
    {
      id: 14,
      question: 'Iran',
      answer: 'Tehran',
    },
    {
      id: 15,
      question: 'Iraq',
      answer: 'Baghdad',
    },
    {
      id: 16,
      question: 'Israel',
      answer: 'Jerusalem',
    },
    {
      id: 17,
      question: 'Japan',
      answer: 'Tokyo',
    },
    {
      id: 18,
      question: 'Jordan',
      answer: 'Amman',
    },
    {
      id: 19,
      question: 'Kazakhstan',
      answer: '	Nur-Sultan',
    },
    {
      id: 20,
      question: 'Kuwait',
      answer: 'Kuwait City',
    },
    {
      id: 21,
      question: 'Kyrgyzstan',
      answer: 'Bishkek',
    },
    {
      id: 22,
      question: 'Laos',
      answer: 'Vientiane',
    },
    {
      id: 23,
      question: 'Lebanon',
      answer: 'Beirut',
    },
    {
      id: 24,
      question: 'Malaysia',
      answer: 'Kuala Lumpur',
    },
    {
      id: 25,
      question: 'Maldives',
      answer: 'Male',
    },
    {
      id: 26,
      question: 'Mongolia',
      answer: 'Ulaanbaatar',
    },
    {
      id: 27,
      question: 'Myanmar',
      answer: 'Naypyidaw',
    },
    {
      id: 28,
      question: 'Nepal',
      answer: 'Kathmandu',
    },
    {
      id: 29,
      question: 'North Korea',
      answer: 'Pyongyang',
    },
    {
      id: 30,
      question: 'Oman',
      answer: 'Muscat',
    },
    {
      id: 31,
      question: 'Pakistan',
      answer: 'Islamabad',
    },
    {
      id: 32,
      question: 'Palestine',
      answer: 'Jerusalem',
    },
    {
      id: 33,
      question: 'Philippines',
      answer: 'Manila',
    },
    {
      id: 34,
      question: 'Qatar',
      answer: 'Doha',
    },
    {
      id: 35,
      question: 'Russia',
      answer: 'Moscow',
    },
    {
      id: 36,
      question: 'Saudi Arabia',
      answer: 'Riyadh',
    },
    {
      id: 37,
      question: 'Singapore',
      answer: 'Singapore',
    },
    {
      id: 38,
      question: 'South Korea',
      answer: 'Seoul',
    },
    {
      id: 39,
      question: 'Sri Lanka',
      answer: 'Sri Jayawardenepura Kotte',
    },
    {
      id: 40,
      question: 'Syria',
      answer: 'Damascus',
    },
    {
      id: 41,
      question: 'Taiwan',
      answer: 'Taipei',
    },
    {
      id: 42,
      question: 'Tajikistan',
      answer: 'Dushanbe',
    },
    {
      id: 43,
      question: 'Thailand',
      answer: 'Bangkok',
    },
    {
      id: 44,
      question: 'Timor-Leste',
      answer: 'Dili',
    },
    {
      id: 45,
      question: 'Turkey',
      answer: 'Ankara',
    },
    {
      id: 46,
      question: 'Turkmenistan',
      answer: 'Ashgabat',
    },
    {
      id: 47,
      question: 'United Arab Emirates',
      answer: 'Abu Dhabi',
    },
    {
      id: 48,
      question: 'Uzbekistan',
      answer: 'Tashkent',
    },
    {
      id: 49,
      question: 'Vietnam',
      answer: 'Hanoi',
    },
    {
      id: 50,
      question: 'Yemen',
      answer: "Sana'a'",
    }
    ]
  
    export default ASIA;